<JOB_DATA>
    <JOB>
        <TITLE>Machine Worker</TITLE>
        <COMPANY>Ironvale Manufacturing Plant</COMPANY>
        <CITY>Springfield</CITY>
        <STATE>IL</STATE>
        <TYPE>Full-Time</TYPE>
        <SALARY>$18.50–$21.00 per hour</SALARY>
        <ABOUTUS>At Ironvale Manufacturing, we specialize in precision metal parts for the automotive and aerospace industries. We’re a fast-paced, safety-first environment where quality, teamwork, and a strong work ethic are key.</ABOUTUS>
        <DESCRIPTION>We are looking for a skilled and safety-conscious Machine Operator to operate CNC and hydraulic machinery in accordance with production specifications. The ideal candidate will have a strong attention to detail and the ability to monitor machine performance, making minor adjustments as needed to ensure smooth operation. Responsibilities include inspecting finished products for quality, promptly reporting any defects, and following all safety protocols while using appropriate personal protective equipment (PPE). Maintaining a clean and organized work area is essential to ensure a safe and efficient manufacturing environment.</DESCRIPTION>
        <JOBSUMMARY>We are seeking a dependable Machine Worker to operate, maintain, and troubleshoot industrial machines. The ideal candidate will be mechanically inclined, safety-conscious, and able to work in a high-output setting.</JOBSUMMARY>
        <RESPONSIBILITIES>Operate CNC and hydraulic machines according to specifications
            Monitor machine operation and make minor adjustments as needed
            Inspect finished products for quality and report any defects
            Follow all safety procedures and wear appropriate PPE
            Keep work area clean and organized
            Assist with routine machine maintenance</RESPONSIBILITIES>
        <QUALIFICATIONS>High school diploma or GED required
            1+ years of experience in a manufacturing or machine shop environment preferred
            Ability to read technical drawings and use basic measuring tools
            Comfortable lifting up to 50 lbs and standing for long periods
            Strong attention to detail and time management skills</QUALIFICATIONS>
    </JOB>
    <JOB>
        <TITLE>Production Supervisor – Machine Operations</TITLE>
        <COMPANY>Ironvale Manufacturing Plant</COMPANY>
        <CITY>Springfield</CITY>
        <STATE>IL</STATE>
        <TYPE>Full-Time</TYPE>
        <SALARY>$58,000–$66,000 annually</SALARY>
        <ABOUTUS>Ironvale Manufacturing is a leader in precision metal components for the automotive and aerospace sectors. With a focus on quality, safety, and continuous improvement, we’re committed to investing in our people and providing opportunities for advancement.</ABOUTUS>
        <JOBSUMMARY>We’re seeking a hands-on Production Supervisor to lead our machine operations team during second shift. This role oversees a crew of machine workers, ensuring production goals are met safely and efficiently while maintaining quality standards. The ideal candidate is a strong communicator with a background in manufacturing leadership.</JOBSUMMARY>
        <DESCRIPTION>We are seeking a dedicated and detail-oriented Shift Supervisor to oversee and coordinate the daily operations of machine workers on assigned shifts. The ideal candidate will be responsible for monitoring production schedules and adjusting workloads to ensure timely and efficient output. Key duties include training new employees, enforcing safety and operational protocols, performing regular quality checks, and troubleshooting machinery or process issues as they arise. This role requires close collaboration with maintenance, quality control, and inventory teams to resolve production challenges and maintain smooth operations. The Shift Supervisor will also be responsible for documenting shift performance and reporting directly to the Plant Manager.</DESCRIPTION>
        <RESPONSIBILITIES>Supervise and coordinate daily activities of machine workers on assigned shift
            Monitor production schedules and adjust workloads as needed
            Train new employees and ensure adherence to safety and operational protocols
            Perform quality checks and troubleshoot machine or process issues
            Collaborate with maintenance, quality, and inventory teams to resolve production challenges
            Document shift performance and report to Plant Manager
            Foster a team-oriented environment focused on continuous improvement</RESPONSIBILITIES>
        <QUALIFICATIONS>High school diploma or equivalent required; associate degree or technical certification preferred
            3+ years of experience in a manufacturing environment, with at least 1 year in a leadership role
            Working knowledge of CNC or hydraulic machine operations
            Strong organizational and decision-making skills
            Proficiency in using production management systems and basic MS Office tools</QUALIFICATIONS>
    </JOB>
    <JOB>
        <TITLE></TITLE>
        <COMPANY></COMPANY>
        <CITY></CITY>
        <STATE></STATE>
        <TYPE></TYPE>
        <SALARY></SALARY>
        <ABOUTUS></ABOUTUS>
        <DESCRIPTION></DESCRIPTION>
        <JOBSUMMARY></JOBSUMMARY>
        <RESPONSIBILITIES></RESPONSIBILITIES>
        <QUALIFICATIONS></QUALIFICATIONS>
    </JOB>
</JOB_DATA>